<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Hui Song's Homepage</title><link href="http://songhui.github.io/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="http://songhui.github.io/feeds/news.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>http://songhui.github.io/</id><updated>2015-01-23T09:20:00+01:00</updated><entry><title>The 2nd-year review of Broker@Cloud went well</title><link href="http://songhui.github.io/posts/2015/01/23/brokeratcloud2ndreview/" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2015-01-23T09:20:00+01:00</updated><author><name>hui</name></author><id>tag:songhui.github.io,2015-01-23:posts/2015/01/23/brokeratcloud2ndreview/</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;The second review of the FP7 project, Broker@Cloud, was help in Brussels on the 22nd of January. We presented our work of using Dynamic Variability Modeling to support the service failure prevention and recovery on cloud brokerage platforms, and showed a demo of the mechanism on a use case provided by Singular Logic from Greece.&lt;/p&gt;</summary><category term="project"></category><category term="review"></category></entry><entry><title>Short Paper accepted by the NIER track of ICSE 2015</title><link href="http://songhui.github.io/posts/2015/01/20/icsenier14/" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2015-01-20T20:20:00+01:00</updated><author><name>hui</name></author><id>tag:songhui.github.io,2015-01-20:posts/2015/01/20/icsenier14/</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;A DIVERSIFY paper titled &lt;em&gt;On Architectural Diversity of Dynamic Adaptive Systems&lt;/em&gt; is accepted by the New Ideas and Emerging Results (NIER) track of ICSE 2015. It is a report of our New Idea to estimate the cost of adapting a running system by measure the system's &lt;strong&gt;diversity&lt;/strong&gt;, which is a measurement borrowed from ecology, using the famous Shannon Index. This is a joint work between SINTEF and TCD, under the FP7-FET project, DIVERSIFY. This time, the paper is accepted with quite positive reviews (two strong accepts and a weak accept), which can be regarded as a good start for our research this this new and interesting direction.&lt;/p&gt;</summary><category term="new paper"></category><category term="icse"></category><category term="diversify"></category></entry><entry><title>Demo paper accepted at SASO 2014</title><link href="http://songhui.github.io/posts/2014/07/28/saso/" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2014-07-28T21:43:00+02:00</updated><author><name>hui</name></author><id>tag:songhui.github.io,2014-07-28:posts/2014/07/28/saso/</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;A short paper, &lt;em&gt;Dynamic Adaptation of the Traffic Management System CARDEMO&lt;/em&gt;, has been accepted at the demo track of the Eighth IEEE International Conference on Self-Adaptive and Self-Organizing Systems (SASO 2014). The paper reports our experiment to apply the constraint-based adaptation approach on a Traffic Management System. It is a joint work between TCD and UCD.&lt;/p&gt;</summary><category term="new paper"></category><category term="models"></category></entry><entry><title>Paper accepted at MODELS 2014</title><link href="http://songhui.github.io/posts/2014/07/27/models14/" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2014-07-27T13:58:00+02:00</updated><author><name>hui</name></author><id>tag:songhui.github.io,2014-07-27:posts/2014/07/27/models14/</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Our paper, &lt;em&gt;Modelling Adaptation Policies as Domain-Specific Constraints&lt;/em&gt;, has been accepted by ACM/IEEE 17th International Conference on Model Driven Engineering Languages and Systems (MODELS 2014).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The paper presented our attempt to apply SMT constraint solving on dynamic system adaptation planning, in the cloud computing domain. We provide a text-based language based on MOF and OCL to support the specification of adaptation policies, and provide a model transformation engine to transform these policies into an SMT problem. Finally, we use SMT solver to compute new state to satisfy as many adaptation constraints as possible. This new state is the adaptation result.&lt;/p&gt;</summary><category term="new paper"></category><category term="models"></category></entry><entry><title>Ran the second leg of Holmenkollstafetten relay race</title><link href="http://songhui.github.io/posts/2014/05/23/holmenkollstafetten/" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2014-05-23T23:53:00+02:00</updated><author><name>hui</name></author><id>tag:songhui.github.io,2014-05-23:posts/2014/05/23/holmenkollstafetten/</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;According to &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Relay_race#Competitions"&gt;Wikipedia&lt;/a&gt;, Holmenkollstafetten is the biggest relay race in the world. This year, it is said that there were almost 40k people running around the &lt;a href="http://www.holmenkollstafetten.no/index.php/loypekart.html"&gt;around the city of Oslo&lt;/a&gt;. It was an interesting experience to be one of these people. Well, I guess this was my first contribution to SINTEF.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I was actually worried a bit before about whether I could finish the 1100 meters, a uphill slope with a 50-meters vertical drop. That was almost like climbing 15 floors, running (there are even some legs much worse than this one: such as 1700 meters with 100 meter drop). So, it was quite a surprise to me to know that I was finally ranked 733 out of 1500 people running Leg 2.&lt;/p&gt;</summary><category term="sintef"></category></entry><entry><title>Homepage Established</title><link href="http://songhui.github.io/posts/2014/04/12/established/" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2014-04-12T14:04:00+02:00</updated><author><name>hui</name></author><id>tag:songhui.github.io,2014-04-12:posts/2014/04/12/established/</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;After being lazy for more than half a year, I finally decided to set-up a new homepage. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now most of the standard content in a "researcher's" homepage are there. I know it is too boring at this stage, but at least I have something to put when they want a "homepage link". Hopefully this webpage will live longer than any of my old ones.&lt;/p&gt;</summary><category term="website"></category></entry></feed>